Guide to the Records of the Student Senators Council RG.44.0.1
New York University Archives
- Series II: Committees and Boards, 1976-2015; 40.78 Linear Feet in 92 manuscript boxes and 1 half manuscript box
  - Interdormitory Council: Proposal, 1983-1984 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Loeb Student Center Advisory Board, 1983-1984 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Senators-at-Large (Senate Executive Committee), 1983-1984 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1983-1984 (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - University Image Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 164, Folder 9-10)
  - Washington Square News Task Force, 1983-1984 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1984 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1984-1985 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS), 1984-1985 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1984-1985 (Box 165, Folder 5-6, Box 166, Folder 1-4)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC) Budget Requests, 1984-1985 (Box 166, Folder 5, Box 167, Folder 1-2)
  - Communications Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee: SSC, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Council, 1984-1989 (Box 247, Folder 6)
  - Financial Affairs, 1984-1985 (Box 247, Folder 7)
  - Food Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Image Task Force, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Independent Student Coalition, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 8)
  - School Student Councils, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 9)
  - Senate Executive Committee Materials, 1984-1985 (Box 167, Folder 10)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1984-1985 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1984-1985 (Box 168, Folder 2-3)
  - Summary of Committees: UCSL & SSC, 1984-1985 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Summary of Committee: University Senate, 1984-1985 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - University Image Task Force, 1984-1985 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Academic Affairs (Senate), 1985-1986 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1985-1986 (Box 169, Folder 1-2)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS), 1985-1986 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Asian Club, 1985-1986 (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - Committee Summaries: Senate Only, 1985-1986 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Committee Summaries: SSC/UCSL Comm., 1985-1986 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Communications Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Council, 1985-1986 (Box 247, Folder 8, Box 248, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council Housing Committee, 1985-1988 (Box 248, Folder 2-6)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Humanities Council, 1985-1986 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1985-1986 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Independent Student Coalition (ISC), 1985-1986 (Box 169, Folder 9-10)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 169, Folder 11, Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1985-1986 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB) Report, 1985-1989 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1985-1986 (Box 170, Folder 4-5)
  - Student Services Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Substance Abuse Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (TSOA) Graduate Student Council, 1985-1986 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - United Staff Association, 1985-1986 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Council, 1986 (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1986-1987 (Box 171, Folder 4-5)
  - Calendar Task Force, 1986-1987 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Coles Advisory Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Communications Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - Drug Education Program, 1986-1987 (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Council Administrative Files, 1986-1987 (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - Gay Lesbian Union, 1986-1987 (Box 171, Folder 12)
  - Independent Student Coalition, 1986-1987 (Box 172, Folder 1-2)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1986-1987 (Box 171, Folder 13)
  - NYU's Mission re: Research ad hoc Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - NYU Security Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Public Affairs, 1986-1987 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Recreation Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - School of Continuing Education (SCE) Student Council, 1986-1987 (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - School Student Councils, 1986-1987 (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - Southern Methodist Conference - American Association of University Students, 1986-1987 (Box 172, Folder 3-4)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1986-1987 (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1986-1987 (Box 172, Folder 12, Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Student/Faculty Relations Committee Ad Hoc, 1986-1987 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Substance Abuse Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Tisch School of the Arts (TSOA) Graduate Student Council, 1986-1987 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC) Contingency Funding, 1987 (Box 173, Folder 5-6)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - AIDS Advisory Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1987-1988 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS), 1987-1988 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Campus Child Care Task Force, 1987-1988 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Child Care Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 174, Folder 3-4)
  - Club Sports Council, 1987-1988 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Coles Advisory BD/Recreation Comm., 1987-1988 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Communications Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Housing Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council, 1987-1988 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - NYU Student Lobby Association (NYUSLA), 1987-1988 (Box 175, Folder 3-4)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 175, Folder 5-6)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1987-1988 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Student AIDS Coalition, 1987-1988 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Student Services Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Student Tuition Assistance Program (TAP) (Independent Student Coalition), 1987-1988 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Substance Abuse Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Summary of SSC/UCSL Committees, 1987-1988 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Council, 1988 (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - AIDS Advisory Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Alcohol/Drug Abuse, 1988-1989 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1988-1989 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS), 1988-1989 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - College of Arts & Sciences (CAS), Student Groups, Budgets, 1988-1989 (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - Coles Recreation Board, 1988-1989 (Box 176, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council, 1988-1989 (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - Finance Affairs Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 176, Folder 12)
  - Gallatin Division: Advisory Board, 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Housing Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Independent Student Coalition - NYU Student Lobby (ISC/NYU SLA), 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - Senate Committees: Summary, 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - SSC/UCSL Committees: Summary, 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 10)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 11-12)
  - Student Services Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 13)
  - University Athletic Association (UAA), 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 14)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 177, Folder 15)
  - AIDS Advisory Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS), 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 3-6)
  - C Team (Chancellor Student Volunteers), 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Coles Advisory Board (Recreation), 1989-1990 (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Health Services/Health Affairs Advisory Board, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Housing Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Independent Student Coalition: NYU Student Lobby (ISC-NYUSLA), NYU in Albany, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Judicial Board, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - Senate Committees: Summary, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 10)
  - Spring Fever Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 11)
  - SSC/UCSL Committees: Summary, 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 12)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 13)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1989-1990 (Box 179, Folder 14-15, Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Student Services Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Substance Abuse Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - University Athletic Association (UAA), 1989-1990 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Yearbook Coordinating Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - Conference Committee, 1990 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Conference Committee - American Association of University Students (AAUS) Conference, 1990 (Box 180, Folder 7-8)
  - Conference Committee - American Association of University Students (AAUS) Conference Materials, 1990 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Conference Committee - American Association of University Students (AAUS) Conference Photographs, 1990 (Box 180, Folder 9-10)
  - Faculty Student Council Photograph Contact Sheet, 1990 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - SSC-UCSL, 1990 (Box Shared University Archives 098, Audiocassette 44.0.1_0013)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1990-1991 (Box 181, Folder 7-8)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS), 1990-1991 (Box 182, Folder 1-3)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS) Conference, 1990-1991 (Box 181, Folder 3-5)
  - Childcare Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 182, Folder 5-6)
  - Faculty Council, 1990-1991 (Box 249, Folder 5-6)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Health Affairs Advisory Board, 1990-1991 (Box 182, Folder 8, Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Independent Student Coalition: NYU Student Lobby (ISC-NYUSLA), 1990-1991 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1990-1991 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Recreation Committee/Coles Advisory Board, 1990-1991 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Search Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1990-1991 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1990-1991 (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Ultraviolet Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1991-1992 (Box 183, Folder 11-12)
  - American Association of University Students (AAUS), 1991-1992 (Box 183, Folder 13)
  - Childcare Task Force, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Communications Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Organization and Governance, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Election Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - External Affairs Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Faculty/Student Relations: Oliva (Special Committee), 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Affairs (Graduate Social Committee), 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - Health Affairs Advisory Board, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 11)
  - Independent Student Coalition: NYU Student Lobby (ISC-NYUSLA), 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 12)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 13)
  - Recreation Committee/Coles Advisory Board, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 14)
  - Special Interest Housing Board, 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 15)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 16)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1991-1992 (Box 184, Folder 17, Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square Park & Community: Oliva (Village Improvement Planning Committee, VIP) (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - AIDS Advisory Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - All Square Budget Allocation Committee (ASSABC), 1992-1993 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Alumni/Student Relations Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Coles Advisory Board (Recreation Committee), 1992-1993 (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Community Service, Special Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Election Committee (School Elections), 1992-1993 (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 185, Folder 10, Box 186, Folder 1)
  - External Affairs Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Financial Aid Office Advisory Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Health Affairs Advisory Board, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Housing Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 9)
  - Judicial Board, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 10)
  - Office of Student Activities (OSA), 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 11)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 12)
  - Resource Planning Group, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 13)
  - Special Interest Housing Board, 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 14)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 15)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1992-1993 (Box 186, Folder 16, Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Student Council, 1992-1993 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Student/Faculty Relations Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Student Grievance Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Substance Abuse Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Washington Square News/Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1992-1993 (Box 187, Folder 6-7)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - AIDS Advisory Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1993-1994 (Box 187, Folder 10-11)
  - Coles Advisory Board (Recreation Committee), 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Communications Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Community Service, Special Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Council on Community Service, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Election Committee (School Election), 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - External Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Financial Aid Office Advisory Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 11)
  - Grievance Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 249, Folder 7)
  - Health Affairs Advisory Board, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 12)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 13)
  - Judicial Board, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 14)
  - Office of Student Activities (OSA), 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 15)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 16)
  - Ruth's Picnic: Advisory Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 17)
  - Special Interest Housing Board, 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 18)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1993-1994 (Box 188, Folder 19)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1993-1994 (Box 189, Folder 1-3)
  - Student Council, 1993-1994 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Student Grievance Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Student Services Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee Ad Hoc, 1993-1994 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1994-1995 (Box 190, Folder 2-5, Box 249, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Relations Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1994-1995 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Communications Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Community Service Council, 1994-1995 (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - Election Committee (School Election), 1994-1995 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 191, Folder 2-3)
  - Financial Affairs, 1994-1995 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 1994-1995 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Affairs, 1994-1995 (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Health Affairs Advisory Board, 1994-1995 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - Inter Greek Council (ICG), 1994-1995 (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1994-1995 (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - Judicial Board, 1994-1995 (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - Office of Student Activities (OSA), 1994-1995 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Public Affairs, 1994-1995 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Special Interest Housing Board, 1994-1995 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1994-1995 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1994-1995 (Box 192, Folder 5-6)
  - Student Health Subcommittee, 1994-1995 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 192, Folder 8, Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Village Improvement Planning VIP, 1994-1995 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1995-1996 (Box 193, Folder 3-5)
  - Alumni Relations Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1995-1996 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Communications Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Community Service Council, 1995-1996 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Election Committee (School Election), 1995-1996 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - EQUAL Commission, 1995-1996 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 194, Folder 5-8)
  - Financial Affairs, 1995-1996 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 1995-1996 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Health Affairs Advisory Board, 1995-1996 (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 1995-1996 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council, 1995-1996 (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - Judicial Board, 1995-1996 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Office of Student Activities (OSA), 1995-1996 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 195, Folder 9)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1995-1996 (Box 195, Folder 10-11)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1995-1996 (Box 196, Folder 1-3)
  - Student Councils, 1995-1996 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Student Grievance Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - Student Health Subcommittee, 1995-1996 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Student Services (food, health committee), 1995-1996 (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Washington Square News, 1995-1996 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Academic Service Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1996-1997 (Box 197, Folder 4-5)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1996-1997 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Communications Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - Community Service Council, 1996-1997 (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - Election Committee (School Election), 1996-1997 (Box 197, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 198, Folder 1-3)
  - Financial Affairs Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Financial Aid Office Advisory Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 1996-1997 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Grievance Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Health Affairs Advisory Board, 1996-1997 (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - Housing Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - Inter Greek Council (IGC), 1996-1997 (Box 198, Folder 10)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1996-1997 (Box 198, Folder 11)
  - Judicial Board, 1996-1997 (Box 198, Folder 12)
  - Program Board, 1996-1997 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1996-1997 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1996-1997 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1996-1997 (Box 199, Folder 4-5)
  - Student Councils, 1996-1997 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Student Health Subcommittee, 1996-1997 (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1997-1998 (Box 200, Folder 2-3)
  - Alumni Relations Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1997-1998 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Communications Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Election Committee (School Election), 1997-1998 (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 200, Folder 8-9, Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Financial Aid Office Advisory Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Food Advisory Board (FAB), 1997-1998 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Graduate Affairs Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Health Affairs Advisory Board, 1997-1998 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Inter Greek Council (ICG), 1997-1998 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Inter Residence Hall Council (IRHC), 1997-1998 (Box 201, Folder 7-8)
  - Judicial Board, 1997-1998 (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Media Task Force, 1997-1998 (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Student Activities Board (SAB), 1997-1998 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Student Affairs Budget Advisory Committee (SABAC), 1997-1998 (Box 202, Folder 3-4)
  - Student Councils, 1997-1998 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - Students for Education and Animal Liberation (SEAL) - Grievance File, 1997-1998 (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Affairs Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 202, Folder 6, Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - Affirmative Action Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 203, Folder Unknown)
  - All Square Student Activities Budget Committee (ASSABC), 1998-1999 (Box 203, Folder 4-5)
  - Alumni Relations Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 203, Folder 6, Box 204, Folder 1-2)
  - Coles Advisory Board, 1998-1999 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Communications Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Election Committee (School Election), 1998-1999 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 204, Folder 6-7, Box 205, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council - Personnel & Aff. Act File 2 of 2, 1998-1999 (Box 205, Folder 2-5)
  - Financial Affairs, 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - Financial Aid Office Advisory Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 206, Folder 2)